<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Jason Cui</title>
 <link href="http://jasoncui.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://jasoncui.me/"/>
 <updated>2016-01-14T16:05:06-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://jasoncui.me</id>
 <author>
   <name>Jason Cui</name>
   <email>jasoncui@college.harvard.edu</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>An Analysis of YC Companies</title>
   <link href="http://jasoncui.me/analysis-of-YC-companies"/>
   <updated>2016-01-14T16:05:05-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://jasoncui.me/analysis-of-YC-companies</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ycombinator.com/&quot;&gt;Y Combinator&lt;/a&gt; (YC) is perhaps the most well-known startup seed accelerator in the world. YC makes $120k seed investments in small groups of startups twice a year in Silicon Valley. The following is a hopefully interesting analysis of YC companies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;http://ajax.googleapis.com/ajax/libs/jquery/1.8.2/jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;http://code.highcharts.com/highcharts.js&quot;&gt;
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;http://code.highcharts.com/modules/exporting.js&quot;&gt;
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;container&quot; style=&quot;min-width: 310px; height: 400px; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
$(&#39;#container&#39;).highcharts({
        chart: {
            type: &#39;column&#39;
        },
        title: {
            text: &#39;Browser market shares. January, 2015 to May, 2015&#39;
        },
        subtitle: {
            text: &#39;Click the columns to view versions. Source: &lt;a href=&quot;http://netmarketshare.com&quot;&gt;netmarketshare.com&lt;/a&gt;.&#39;
        },
        xAxis: {
            type: &#39;category&#39;
        },
        yAxis: {
            title: {
                text: &#39;Total percent market share&#39;
            }

        },
        legend: {
            enabled: false
        },
        plotOptions: {
            series: {
                borderWidth: 0,
                dataLabels: {
                    enabled: true,
                    format: &#39;{point.y:.1f}%&#39;
                }
            }
        },

        tooltip: {
            headerFormat: &#39;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:11px&quot;&gt;{series.name}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#39;,
            pointFormat: &#39;&lt;span style=&quot;color:{point.color}&quot;&gt;{point.name}&lt;/span&gt;: &lt;b&gt;{point.y:.2f}%&lt;/b&gt; of total&lt;br/&gt;&#39;
        },

        series: [{
            name: &#39;Brands&#39;,
            colorByPoint: true,
            data: [{
                name: &#39;Microsoft Internet Explorer&#39;,
                y: 56.33,
                drilldown: &#39;Microsoft Internet Explorer&#39;
            }, {
                name: &#39;Chrome&#39;,
                y: 24.03,
                drilldown: &#39;Chrome&#39;
            }, {
                name: &#39;Firefox&#39;,
                y: 10.38,
                drilldown: &#39;Firefox&#39;
            }, {
                name: &#39;Safari&#39;,
                y: 4.77,
                drilldown: &#39;Safari&#39;
            }, {
                name: &#39;Opera&#39;,
                y: 0.91,
                drilldown: &#39;Opera&#39;
            }, {
                name: &#39;Proprietary or Undetectable&#39;,
                y: 0.2,
                drilldown: null
            }]
        }],
        drilldown: {
            series: [{
                name: &#39;Microsoft Internet Explorer&#39;,
                id: &#39;Microsoft Internet Explorer&#39;,
                data: [
                    [
                        &#39;v11.0&#39;,
                        24.13
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v8.0&#39;,
                        17.2
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v9.0&#39;,
                        8.11
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v10.0&#39;,
                        5.33
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v6.0&#39;,
                        1.06
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v7.0&#39;,
                        0.5
                    ]
                ]
            }, {
                name: &#39;Chrome&#39;,
                id: &#39;Chrome&#39;,
                data: [
                    [
                        &#39;v40.0&#39;,
                        5
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v41.0&#39;,
                        4.32
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v42.0&#39;,
                        3.68
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v39.0&#39;,
                        2.96
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v36.0&#39;,
                        2.53
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v43.0&#39;,
                        1.45
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v31.0&#39;,
                        1.24
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v35.0&#39;,
                        0.85
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v38.0&#39;,
                        0.6
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v32.0&#39;,
                        0.55
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v37.0&#39;,
                        0.38
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v33.0&#39;,
                        0.19
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v34.0&#39;,
                        0.14
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v30.0&#39;,
                        0.14
                    ]
                ]
            }, {
                name: &#39;Firefox&#39;,
                id: &#39;Firefox&#39;,
                data: [
                    [
                        &#39;v35&#39;,
                        2.76
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v36&#39;,
                        2.32
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v37&#39;,
                        2.31
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v34&#39;,
                        1.27
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v38&#39;,
                        1.02
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v31&#39;,
                        0.33
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v33&#39;,
                        0.22
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v32&#39;,
                        0.15
                    ]
                ]
            }, {
                name: &#39;Safari&#39;,
                id: &#39;Safari&#39;,
                data: [
                    [
                        &#39;v8.0&#39;,
                        2.56
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v7.1&#39;,
                        0.77
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v5.1&#39;,
                        0.42
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v5.0&#39;,
                        0.3
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v6.1&#39;,
                        0.29
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v7.0&#39;,
                        0.26
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v6.2&#39;,
                        0.17
                    ]
                ]
            }, {
                name: &#39;Opera&#39;,
                id: &#39;Opera&#39;,
                data: [
                    [
                        &#39;v12.x&#39;,
                        0.34
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v28&#39;,
                        0.24
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v27&#39;,
                        0.17
                    ],
                    [
                        &#39;v29&#39;,
                        0.16
                    ]
                ]
            }]
        }
    });

&lt;/script&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My Hope for DC Tech in 2016</title>
   <link href="http://jasoncui.me/my-hope-for-DC-tech"/>
   <updated>2016-01-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://jasoncui.me/my-hope-for-DC-tech</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jasoncui.me/public/washington.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;DC&quot; class=&quot;center-image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This holiday season DC Inno published &lt;a href=&quot;http://dcinno.streetwise.co/2015/12/24/dc-tech-startup-wishlist-2016/&quot;&gt;a wish list&lt;/a&gt; of things it’d like to see happen with the DC tech community in 2016. I thought it would be interesting to publish a similar post, from a younger (and perhaps more inexperienced) perspective.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A bit of background to understand where I’m coming from. I’m currently a sophomore at Harvard studying computer science. Born and bred in Northern Virginia, I’ve worked at both a startup (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.prepfactory.com/&quot;&gt;PrepFactory&lt;/a&gt;) and large tech company (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.livingsocial.com/&quot;&gt;LivingSocial&lt;/a&gt;) in the capital. I also started my own non-profit (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.joindcxp.org/&quot;&gt;DCXP&lt;/a&gt;) in the area to cultivate talented high school and college students, an attempt to strengthen DC’s tech community from the ground up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through my various work experiences and time networking with entrepreneurs, VCs, and angel investors through DCXP, I’ve left with mixed feelings. On one hand, I feel a deep sense of &lt;strong&gt;pride and belonging&lt;/strong&gt;. It’s inspiring to see life-changing innovation and wildly successful companies grow just steps away from where I grew up. And for that I am extremely grateful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, I see a lot of room for improvement. I think the DC, Maryland, and Virginia (DMV) area has a lot to offer and is poised to really develop rapidly in the coming years. In the years to follow, I want to see more talented individuals set-up shop in the area and to build great companies, create new jobs, and foster a stronger tech community in what is already a very substantial one. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few things I believe would help the area further progress in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;more-seed-funding-in-the-dmv&quot;&gt;More seed funding in the DMV.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is pretty self-explanatory and is the same thought echoed by DC Inno’s article. More seed money means more early-stage companies. More early-stage companies means more talent and interest drawn to the area. 	&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is somewhat unclear why seed funding is lacking at the moment. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nea.com/team/harry-weller&quot;&gt;Harry Weller&lt;/a&gt; of New Enterprise Associates and &lt;a href=&quot;http://nav.vc/team/john-backus/&quot;&gt;John Backus&lt;/a&gt; of New Atlantic Ventures claim a “lack of large exits” means less wealthy individuals who can act as angel investors and write smaller checks pre-series A/B. Perhaps individuals are flocking to areas outside of DC – the Valley, NYC, and Boston because they know that funding is more plentiful there, especially on a smaller scale. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless, there is definitely room for improvement. A clear solution has not immediately materialized, but I believe the rise of incubators and co-working spaces in the area is a push in the right direction. See &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.1776.vc&quot;&gt;1776&lt;/a&gt; in DC and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wework.com/locations/washington-d-c&quot;&gt;WeWork&lt;/a&gt; offices in the area as great examples. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;successful-ipos&quot;&gt;Successful IPOs.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again this seems relatively self-explanatory, and is more of a &lt;em&gt;fingers crossed&lt;/em&gt; hope than an actionable goal. Current sentiment is more negative than positive, but there are rumors of multiple companies potentially IPOing in 2016. Notable ones include &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.appian.com/&quot;&gt;Appian&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.clarabridge.com/&quot;&gt;Clarabridge&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://optoro.com/&quot;&gt;Optoro&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencelogic.com/&quot;&gt;ScienceLogic&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.voxmedia.com/&quot;&gt;Vox Media&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sonatype.com/&quot;&gt;SonaType&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-greater-focus-on-attracting-cultivating-and-retaining-young-talent&quot;&gt;A greater focus on attracting, cultivating, and retaining young talent.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is something I firmly believe in and am personally passionate about. Startup dogma states that a solid team is one of the most important pillars of a successful company. And for startups just getting off the ground in the area, finding and retaining a long-term team is not always an easy task. From talking to many young entrepreneurs (both personal friends and acquaintances), they describe the current status quo as one where founders in the DC area want to stay close to home, but end up going elsewhere to better attract cofounders and technical talent. A great example is early-stage teams traveling to incubators and accelerators elsewhere, notably &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ycombinator.com/&quot;&gt;Y Combinator&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.techstars.com/&quot;&gt;TechStars&lt;/a&gt;, and end up relocating as a result. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me this is a great shame. There is so much local talent from universities, even from the high school level in the DMV that remains untapped. This is one of the main reasons why I co-founded &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.joindcxp.org&quot;&gt;DCXP&lt;/a&gt; along with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/brian-mitchell-6b8704a2&quot;&gt;Brian Mitchell&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/danny-flax-143a2b3a&quot;&gt;Danny Flax&lt;/a&gt;. We &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@joindcxp/why-we-started-dcxp-e15fe06fd311#.94h76ohj5&quot;&gt;write about that experience here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jasoncui.me/public/dcxp.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;DC&quot; class=&quot;center-image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The DCXP team hard at work.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DCXP is a rapidly-paced bootcamp for talented technical students where they run through workshops, prototyping sprints, and collaborate to build amazing software products. This summer, we had a team of less than 15 high school and college students build the MVP for a bike sharing startup in &lt;em&gt;less than three weeks&lt;/em&gt;. That company was &lt;a href=&quot;http://baasbikes.com/&quot;&gt;Baas Bikes&lt;/a&gt;. The fact that students (many of whom aren’t even old enough to drive!) built a functional prototype that quickly is energizing and testament to the talent available in the DMV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tapping into this talent in years to come will be a deciding factor for the future success of this community.&lt;/strong&gt; Hopefully DCXP will continue to thrive in the area, and similar programs will encourage talented students to stick around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;continue-to-fight-the-preconceived-notion-that-the-area-is-home-to-only-government-and-contracting&quot;&gt;Continue to fight the preconceived notion that the area is home to only government and contracting.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this is a pretty outdated idea that still seems to be thrown around in conversations about tech in the area. While it’s true that the local tech scene is less prominent in comparison to other hubs around the country, so much has already been done to create a strong community. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tech publications have played a large role in strengthening the sense of community (much gratitude to the likes of &lt;a href=&quot;http://dcinno.streetwise.co/&quot;&gt;DC Inno&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://tech.co/&quot;&gt;Tech.co&lt;/a&gt; and others). Writing more about the community and the key players in the area will continue to help interest and awareness develop. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;If you liked this post, you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?url=http://jasoncui.me/my-hope-for-DC-tech&amp;amp;text=My Hope for DC Tech in 2016&amp;amp;via=jasonscui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  share it with your followers&lt;/a&gt; 
or 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jasonscui&quot;&gt;
  follow me on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A Guide to Startup Internships</title>
   <link href="http://jasoncui.me/guide-to-startup-internships"/>
   <updated>2016-01-10T23:49:06-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://jasoncui.me/a-guide-to-startup-internships</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Test&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How I Made This Blog (For Free)</title>
   <link href="http://jasoncui.me/2015/12/23/how-i-made-this-blog-for-free/"/>
   <updated>2015-12-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://jasoncui.me/2015/12/23/how-i-made-this-blog-for-free</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I’ve had a lot of people ask me how I made this blog for free. Below I outline some of the steps I took. Hopefully this serves as a helpful resource to those looking to start a personal blog of their own.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I mention in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jasoncui.me/about&quot;&gt;about section&lt;/a&gt;, this site was built with &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://getpoole.com/&quot;&gt;Poole&lt;/a&gt; and is hosted (for free) with &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com&quot;&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt;. I’ll do my best to gather all the resources I used to build this site. Feel free to leave any questions or comments in the comment section below (which should be working with Disqus integration). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As to why I chose this method of blogging in particular, I was definitely considering a more user-friendly blogging platform (Wordpress, Squarespace, etc.) but decided to go with Jekyll/Github pages because I didn’t want to pay, and wanted the additional customizability. I also liked the minimalistic style of &lt;a href=&quot;http://getpoole.com/&quot;&gt;Poole&lt;/a&gt;. Uploading posts is definitely a tougher process, but hopefully this pans out to be a fun project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;resources&quot;&gt;Resources&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This site wouldn’t have been possible without the helpful documentation and walkthroughs available online. Below are a few of the resources I used: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Documentation&lt;/a&gt;. A useful overview of what Jekyll is. Useful tips ranging from content creation to customization.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://getpoole.com/&quot;&gt;Poole Homepage&lt;/a&gt;. Poole is the Jekyll theme used for this site. The homepage contains demos and variations on the main Poole theme you can also use. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://joshualande.com/jekyll-github-pages-poole/&quot;&gt;Joshua Lande’s Tutorial&lt;/a&gt;. A great resource from Joshua Lande detailing how to set-up a Jekyll blog with Poole from start to finish. &lt;strong&gt;This source in itself is extensive enough.&lt;/strong&gt; Also has cool tips about setting up extra features like Google Analytics, comments, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sitepoint.com/set-jekyll-blog-5-minutes-poole/&quot;&gt;Vikas Lalwani’s Tutorial&lt;/a&gt;. A similar walkthrough-style post that details how to set-up a Jekyll blog.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is a “static site generator” that runs with Ruby under the hood. It takes content that is formatted in Markdown (a markup language using plain text) and from that generates a static site. &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/github-pages/&quot;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt; uses Jekyll which allows users to host and publish content for free. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;poole&quot;&gt;Poole&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jasoncui.me/public/poole.png&quot; alt=&quot;Poole&quot; class=&quot;center-image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As mentioned above, &lt;a href=&quot;http://getpoole.com/&quot;&gt;Poole&lt;/a&gt; is the Jekyll theme used for this site. Poole also contains two official themes within it called &lt;em&gt;Hyde&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Landon&lt;/em&gt; that offer additional features ranging from two-column themes to hidden navigation bars. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;url&quot;&gt;URL&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately this section will apply only to students. Namecheap for Education offers a free .me domain to students with a .edu address. You can get your free .me domain &lt;a href=&quot;https://nc.me/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the domain from Namecheap, it is easy to configure Namecheap DNS for Github pages. A good tutorial for that process can be found &lt;a href=&quot;http://abdelraoof.com/blog/2014/09/20/configuring-namecheap-dns-for-github/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be sure to read through all the resources before setting up a site - many of the links guide you through the entire process quite well. In the future I’d love to figure out how to tag posts and then sort by category. Thanks for reading! &lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Working with HelloToken</title>
   <link href="http://jasoncui.me/2015/10/09/working-with-hellotoken/"/>
   <updated>2015-10-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://jasoncui.me/2015/10/09/working-with-hellotoken</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/hellotoken.png&quot; alt=&quot;HelloToken Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, I  was brought on board &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hellotoken.com&quot;&gt;HelloToken&lt;/a&gt; as a part of the business development team. For now I’ll be working with them for the rest of the semester for the fall term. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, there has been some &lt;a href=&quot;http://venturefizz.com/blog/hellotoken-changing-way-we-monetize-content&quot;&gt;cool&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.betaboston.com/news/2015/09/08/by-posing-questions-to-website-visitors-boston-based-hellotoken-hopes-to-supply-answer-to-revenue-quandary/&quot;&gt;press&lt;/a&gt; on HelloToken. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-exactly-does-hellotokenhttpwwwhellotokencom-do&quot;&gt;What exactly does &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hellotoken.com&quot;&gt;HelloToken&lt;/a&gt; do?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Essentially, HelloToken is a product that enables publishers to earn exponentially more per visitor than ads and paywalls through a one-click question that serves as a micropayment. As daily consumers of content, nothing is more distracting and unaesthetic than intrusive advertisements or blurred out paywalls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HelloToken can replace all obtrusive advertisements on a site with a clean, one-click question that when answered will give immediate access to that page’s content. Researchers and companies will pay to ask questions relevant to them - for instance, a startup might be interested in “preference testing” which one of their new logo designs is more appealing. These questions can then be sent off to the proper target audience, whether it be a technology or political blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Publishers and bloggers can then use these questions as a form of monetization. By integrating HelloToken into their sites, publishers can be paid for each question answered by visitors to the sites. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below is a cool video about HelloToken:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/PcfSZmo3ZP0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-hellotokenhttpwwwhellotokencoms-current-strategy-and-plans-for-expansion&quot;&gt;What is &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hellotoken.com&quot;&gt;HelloToken&lt;/a&gt;’s current strategy and plans for expansion?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of now HelloToken is based in Boston and working out of Harvard’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://i-lab.harvard.edu/&quot;&gt;i-lab&lt;/a&gt;, a great collaborative coworking space. With a little bit of angel funding under its belt, its looking to build up the team in terms of engineers, business development, content and design. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Around 60 or so publishers have also been signed on, with the focus now being put on researchers and startups who might utilize the product.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out HelloToken on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/thehellotoken&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hello_token&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and keep up-to-date with progress!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Welcome To My Blog</title>
   <link href="http://jasoncui.me/2015/10/02/welcome-to-my-blog/"/>
   <updated>2015-10-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://jasoncui.me/2015/10/02/welcome-to-my-blog</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my site! My name is Jason Cui and I am a sophomore at Harvard studying computer science. I am passionate about technology, scientific discovery, and entrepreneurship. This site is a collection of my projects, thoughts, and random materials I find interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to reach out on my &lt;a href=&quot;http://jasoncui.me/contact&quot;&gt;contact page&lt;/a&gt; or through my social media handles below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;social&quot;&gt;Social&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jasonscui&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.twitter.com/JasonSCui&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/JasonSCui&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/JasonSCui&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re curious, this site was built with &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://getpoole.com/&quot;&gt;Poole&lt;/a&gt; and is hosted (for free!) with &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com&quot;&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
